Hello everyone!
Seino!
This is Nuuan Life Pokemon Club!
Oh!
We did it, we did it, we did it!
I'm Otamakai, the head of Miyagi Pokemon Club!
This is the second time we've been able to do this activity in March!
We're so glad we did it for the second time, and we've had some fans ask us how it went last time, but it was great, and some of them even bought the same thing.
Some of the fans were so happy that they bought the same thing, and they showed us their goods at the in-person meeting.
I'm so glad to hear that you've prepared these hats for us today. I'm so excited that we've decided to do this project.
This time, we're going to open up our merchandise to the public.
This time, we are happy to introduce the goods that we want to buy.
I'd like to introduce some of the goods we've bought that we'd like to get soon.
Please go with us!
Now, here are the goods we've bought!
It's not so bad... but it's not this big...
I don't get to go to a private party and get something of this size, either.
I wonder what Micchan picked out for me to look forward to?
Oh, sure...
I'll go first.
At first, I think I'll go with this one.
Which one?
Oh.
I think I'm going to go with one of these.
I'm sure you'll be interested.
Okay, then.
The first child, here!
Dururun!
This is Papimocci!
So cute!
Mochi Mochi
It's for sticky men!
Papimocci, well...
The stickier, the better.
And the last one is a bit...
Oh, my gosh!
Glutinous.
You see?
This back, this side.
That's it.
Bread dough.
He's so cute.
Bread dough doggie.
Cute.
He's cute.
They say she's bows when she evolves.
You see this one that's been burned?
I like it because it's also cute.
This big one!
He's so big!
If I could sleep with a sticky baby...
I can have a happy sleep every night.
That's why I got her this time.
Even an adult Ai can sleep early, right?
Yes, I can already!
I'm a night owl.
with this girl.
Twelve.
I'll try to be in bed by 7:00
I will do my best from now on.
Cute, thank you, for wearing it.
I'm over here.
Aah!
Over here!
That's little Niphia.
Oh, that's nice.
You like her, don't you?
Nephia.
I love it. And it's a bit of an update.
She's slender.
Slender.
She's so beautiful.
And the color.
I love the body.
I know.
You know what?
There's a reason why I love it so much.
In the XY cartoon.
Serena and...
King Doll
They call her "Kingdoll", right?
Yes.
I made a ribbon from Nephia's ribbon and wrapped it around her.
Wrapped around it.
My shenanigans.
I love it.
I love that scene.
We had some kind of contest, right?
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's so cute!
He's so cute.
We do it every day.
Me too.
I'm going to bed.
Shall we go? Next.
Hi, Mi-chan.
I see. Do you want to go?
Me?
Yes, I do.
Uh...
I don't think I'll buy it unless it's an opportunity like this.
I don't think I'll buy it.
It's nice, isn't it?
This way, please.
Deden.
Miniature Torso
Wait a minute!
Ha!
Deden.
Wow.
Miiiighty.
Salt.
Salt, am I right?
Tiny Salt
Salt.
It was a tiny salt.
Micrograms.
Wait a minute.
It's like this
It's like this.
I knew it!
This way
It's pretty new, isn't it?
Yes, yes, yes
This kind of thing...
I love figurines.
I know.
Mine is the one from the live show.
This is my number 8, the "Nanjamochan".
It's nice.
I'm Nanjamochan.
Wow, I'm...
I hope you get it.
Buttons
Mr. Buttons
Yes, Mr. Button.
Mr. Button.
Like a button.
I like that.
Okay, let's sing a song.
Do you want to go with "Se-Yo Do"?
Yeah.
Then we'll go at the same time.
Se-ne-ap-ap-ap.
Ta-da!
Oh, what?
What was that?
What was what?
What number, what number, what number?
God's with me.
Uh, what?
Isn't that MOMA? Could it be this one?
What number is this?
Me? Oh, it's Mr. Kibana.
Oh, it's Mr. Kibana.
Oh, it's Kibana.
Oh!
Let's put it together.
You want me to assemble it?
I'm so glad.
I'm fine.
I'm familiar with electricity.
I'm a big fan of little electric Pokemon.
I love them.
When I was watching cartoons back then, I was crazy about Emonger.
I'm so happy because I like it so much that I have a lot of them in my house.
It also comes with an Acsta!
I'm so happy to have you with me!
I don't know.
And it's light yellow!
Oh, I'm sure.
It's from the top.
From the top?
What?
This is...
These are swamps.
Like this...
I'll collect them all.
And then you say, "I want eight different kinds.
I'll collect them.
I'll probably go buy them in private.
Right?
Oh!
Doo-doo!
Doo-doo-doo!
I'm sorry, Emonger.
It was Mr. Thorn and Geraldon
Okay, okay
It just keeps getting better and better.
That's nice.
Okay, so you've got the figure now.
Yes, sir.
But...
There's one more figure I want to give you.
I like to collect them.
I like to collect them a lot
I like to collect them a lot.
This way
Dooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo
I'm so happy!
This is...
Terrarium Collection EX
Running around in the world of Pardea
Oh!
Give it to me.
Oh, yeah?
Let's see...
Oyoyo?
Dendendendendendendendendendendendendendendendendendendendendendendendendendendendend.
D-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d.
Abikami.
Abikami!
I'm so happy!
This is also a rather new design or series
It's called "Pardea".
This time
Cute!
Pamo and Pikachu are already here.
There's Hoge-chan, too.
And Kwassu.
Yeah.
And Nyanha.
Yes.
And Sharitatsu.
It's cute, isn't it?
Domo.
Domo is out.
Domo is my favorite.
I know.
This is...
It's like a shape you can make chocolate in.
What?
I saw it.
Yes.
I want to make one of those for White Day.
You're right.
Like that silico.
Yes, yes, yes.
What do you want?
I'm Nyanha.
Oh, that's nice.
I like Kwassu, and Pikachu is electric, but...
This time, I'm going to get Sharitatsu.
Oh, that's good.
I'm going to do Sharitatsu.
I've already seen three different forms of Sharitatsu, all at once.
So cute!
Yeah, they're all lined up in a row, so it's kind of nice.
Yes, it's a good deal.
Let's go ahead and do it
Touch them.
I know what you mean.
No, I don't know.
It's round.
It's a circle.
They were all circles.
Oh, but what's this?
It feels warm.
Warm.
You want some?
I feel like I have a lot of stink.
Oh, really?
Yeah, I do.
Okay.
Ready?
That's it!
Kwassu.
Oh, wow.
Quass.
Quack.
What the...
What? Hey! Oh! That's what I'm talking about!
The kid inside! That's what I'm talking about!
I'm Kwassu, and this time, I'm traveling with Kwassu as my partner.
As a renewal, I'm a little happy about this.
I'm so happy!
I hope you will become Kwassu's partner.
Yes!
So cute!
Wait, do you have something to offer? I'll help you with that.
You're so cute helping her.
No, he's adorable.
Wait, cute, cute, cute! Look at that.
Like, I'll show you my hands.
Here! The color of the cusps, the cusps are blue, or maybe blue, or maybe blue.
Matching! You and Micchan have matching ones, don't you?
Right! Namimuri!
Nam-Muri Nam-Muri!
I'm so happy!
Let's take a look at this again.
Is it on? Yes, it's here.
So cute!
Thank you so much!
There's a lot more where this came from.
Okay, let's see what we've got.
Anya okashi!
Go for it!
It's so colorful! There are probably all the colors in the world right now.
So colorful that every color in the world is on the screen!
I'm so happy!
Okay, let's continue.
Why do you want to do this? Why do you think?
I just love it.
This one.
Ta-da!
Wow!
It's a pawternomy!
I was on the fence about this one, too.
I was fighting a last minute household battle over whether or not to put it in my basket.
Oh!
Which one!
So cute!
Big! Surprisingly big!
It's silicon!
Twist, twist, twist.
So cute!
Aah! Ah!
It's full of stuff inside, too.
So cute!
The peaches are in the shape of peaches.
Peach-shaped.
It's nice.
So cute!
It's fun to eat.
And when you're done eating it, you can put it in a lot of different ways.
Hey, Mongkokko!
Here we go.
Say, "Don't worry, Mami-Mochi! Say, "Mamimochi!
Mamimochi! Mamimochi!
Hold on! Mami-Mochi!
But it'll last a lifetime.
Great!
Good stuff!
Okay, let's just get this out of the way.
Oh, what's that?
I'd like something a little more compact, please. I think.
Here!
Yes!
The cutlet!
It's already evolved. It's all evolved.
What is this? Is that a metal charm?
It's a metal charm.
Ta-da!
I went to buy this one myself, but I couldn't find the course.
So I thought I'd take this opportunity.
I like to collect these too, like this one on my cell phone.
What is it?
I like to collect these too.
Yes!
I like to put a little bit of this on my heart charm.
I like to put these on my heart charms.
The three Coas charms...
I bought it!
I like the one with Metamon on it.
Yes, I, what's it called?
I put Zoro on it.
Yes, I put Zoro on it, but I thought I'd add it to the group.
So cute!
Well, I think I'll put this out.
What is it?
This way!
Don!
Aah! Coas!
Oh! Nice! Nice Coas!
Socks! Nice!
I saw them at the last Yeju Pokemon Club.
I thought, "What, it's cute!
I thought, I'm actually going to pick them up someday, so I got them this time!
So cute!
I'm kinda putting them away today because I'm not wearing sneakers.
It's my neck.
It's fine.
I'll start tomorrow's lesson.
Wanna wear them?
Yes! You can see right here, right here, in these sneakers.
They're so cute!
I wear these at home.
Coascolo!
I'm wearing these.
I love it when they come out.
It's cute when they come out.
Every time they come out, I think about getting sneakers.
Every time you don't wear sneakers, you'll wear them well, so good!
These, a lot.
These are kinda nice.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
They're nice. They're cute.
Oh, really? All these colors.
They're so cute.
It's fun.
We're going with the practical stuff now, aren't we? I'm going with the practical stuff, too.
This is Metamon. I don't know what to call this one, Metamon.
Just insert it into the case. Just insert it. It's so easy and clear.
I'm about to get a new cell phone, and I really need something to put on my arm, like a string or something.
I'm going to get a new cell phone in a little bit, and if I don't have a string or something to put on my arm, I'm really likely to drop it.
If you put this transparent part between the cell phone case and the cell phone, you can think of this as the cell phone.
So when I'm touching my phone like this...
This is the best product I've ever seen. I got this in the practical product category.
I got this one for practical use, too.
Here's a practical product, Metamon from Makeup Puffs.
Metamon version. Wait a minute.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Deden!
Pikachu! Pikachu! Pikachu!
This is good. I knew it. It's a sponge.
You can have as many as you want. I really do.
And the TARUMA has lots of turbos, so it's easy to use.
This is really good! It fits my face line here!
My Pikachu's ears are here, too.
My Pikachu's ears are right here, so it's easy to use.
It's easy to use.
I'm going to use Metamon at the next show.
I think I've already applied it very evenly on the kobara, I think.
Let's show one thing. You know what?
Let's use a little texture on Metamon.
But I want to do Kobala with Pikachu.
Well, then, if you have any, they'll take them.
This is nice. It's a practical product.
For girls and stuff. Yeah, really.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
I'm Rust. Rust? Yes. How's that?
I've been a little busy.
Go ahead.
This way, please.
The pins and ear cufflinks you need for makeup.
Nice and cute!
Can you hold it?
Sure.
Can I wait for him now?
Just give me a second.
Ear cafe?
You're so cool.
We don't match.
It's so cute.
I like this Pikachu.
No way!
They're matching.
It's a Pikachu.
Isn't this cute?
I like the ear café.
Let's put them on.
I put on my Pod Death today.
It's really cute!
They're so cute!
I've been wearing Poddeath earrings
I've been wearing them as a Pokémon club
There's one over here, too.
You're here?
Oh, it's so cute!
What's this?
Oh, man.
Are you here?
Yeah, I'm here.
Yes, I'm here.
Yes. Yes.
Yes. - Yes.
I'm so happy! It's a nice headband, isn't it?
It looks like it! It's so similar!
It's a little crooked.
I'm pushing it, I'm pushing it, I'm pushing it. It looks like it! Okay.
I put it on! My ears are a little red.
What do you think?
It's so cute!
So cute!
Cockemon is a pretty good accessory
I'm going to make him wear it.
I have a lot of accessories and stuff.
I really want something for myself every time
I always want something new.
This one!
I have to wear this.
I'd be embarrassed if I didn't wear this.
You know what I mean? If you want.
If I don't have this on after today.
Maybe not.
You know, when I go in...
Everyone wears hats.
I don't really want to wear a hat.
I'll wear this.
Good morning.
It's the morning of the concert.
He can do it.
Good morning!
I can clap too
Crackle, crackle, crackle.
Go.
I can take a cab.
I can't stop a cab by myself.
I'm going to ask for Sukachoo's help.
I'd like to stop a cab with the help of Sukachoo.
Great.
That'll make me feel better.
I think I'll just finish up.
Finish up.
That's good.
Here's the last one.
That's it!
Crackle, crackle, crackle!
So cute!
Here's our sleepy friend, Nyonha.
Look at that!
So cute!
Cute!
Cute
There's a lot of Shia-sen series, too.
Cute!
We'll be together with this.
So cute!
Wait.
A dream.
Maybe it's a dream.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Can you take a picture of it?
It's for me.
Please send it to me
Live Broadcast
Miyajii Pokemon Club
Miyaji's Pokemon Club
I'm glad you got a lot of them.
I'm glad we got the second one!
I'm glad we got a second one this time.
I'm so happy that I got a lot of matching items with my friend, Micchan, and I. I'm sure you all want to go to the Pokémon Center, too.
I'm so glad that you watched this video and found yourself in the Pokemon Center.
I'm in the Pokemon Center.
I'm sure you are!
We will make every effort so that we can do it again for the third time.
We will do Poke-activities enthusiastically, so please continue to cooperate with Niyaji's Pokemon club.
If you liked this video and you think I'm the best Pokemon lover, please give me a high rating.
Please give us a high rating!
Please give us a high rating, comment and subscribe to our channel, and we'll see you in the next video!
See you soon!
Thank you for watching!